Phone: 850.345.4128 **Address:** Atlanta, GA 30339

barbara.kelly892@gmail.com

Website: www.linkedin.com/in/barbie-kelly



PROJECT ENGINEER II

About: I have performed investigations related to water intrusion, fire damage, wind damage, and structural failures and collapses. I am experienced in site design for residential and commercial projects of varying scale and complexity, and competent in a variety of computer programs, including Computer Aided Design (CAD) programs, Geographic Information Systems (GIS) programs, and various computer programming languages and technologies. EIT pursuing PE license.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Email:

2019-10- **PROJECT ENGINEER II** Present *JS Held, Alpharetta, GA*

Performing forensic inspections and analysis of structures to provide an engineering evaluation. Writing technical reports in support of the evaluation on the origin, cause, and extent of relevant damages based on field observations and research.

2018-11- PROJECT ENGINEER

2019-10 Ridge Planning and Engineering, Marietta, GA

Civil site design utilizing AutoCAD Civil 3D including site, storm and sanitary design, and Erosion Control. Creating full sets of engineering plans, land planning/

preliminary conceptual designs, and coordination of subcontractors and permitting.

2017-08- **PROJECT ENGINEER**

2018-11 Paragon Consulting Group, Atlanta, GA

Civil site design utilizing AutoCAD Civil 3D including site, grading, storm & sanitary design, and erosion control. Project management for roadway asset management programs for municipal clients. Data collection oversight, data processing, data analytics and visualization with custom forms and maps utilizing ArcGIS and FileMaker Pro.

2015-08- ENGINEERING TECHNICIAN

2016-08 Singhofen & Associates, Orlando, FL

Supporting floodplain management and FEMA mapping through setting up and running hydrologic and hydraulic (h&h) models in ArcGIS & ICPR (H&H modeling program). Writing technical reports utilizing high quality supporting maps, graphics, tables & charts.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2019-01 EROSION AND SEDIMENTATION CONTROL PROGRAM

GASWCC | LEVEL II CERTIFICATION # 0000086326

2017-05 **ENGINEER IN TRAINING CERTIFICATION (EIT)**

State of Georgia | EIT027221

2016-05 BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING

University of Central Florida | 3.7 GPA with Honors